http://www.vantagepointconsult.com/privacy

Contact
Privacy PolicyVantagePoint’s Privacy Policy reflects its intention to respect and protect the private information of our clients and other visitors to our website. To protect online information, VantagePoint has implemented the following policy.It is our policy to collect and store only personal information that our clients and visitors willfully provide to us so that we may keep them informed about new information, products, and services that may be of interest.VantagePoint does not collect information from persons browsing our web site.We use information willfully submitted by clients and users in the following ways. As it relates to our services and products, we will only use the data collected to respond to clients and users inquiries about our services or products or to develop new products or service lines. We will use the information collected to provide clients and users with periodic news items, newsletters and announcements.VantagePoint does not provide any information submitted by clients or users, without their express written consent, to any third parties.VantagePoint does not disclose credit card account information provided by its clients or customers to any entity except to VantagePoint in order to process payment. We do not provide refunds on purchased products.Our website contains links to other web sites and we have no control over, nor are we responsible for the content, practices or procedures of such sites.VantagePoint reserves the right to make changes to this policy at its sole discretion and without prior notice. Any changes to this policy will be posted on our website. Contact with VantagePoint, without requesting exclusion from this Privacy Policy, constitutes acceptance of this Policy. Continued use of any product following any announced changes to the Privacy Policy constitutes acceptance of those changes.To contact us with questions or comments:Email at: info@vantagepointconsult.comPhone: 203.288.6860Fax: 203.288.3283or via mail to: VantagePoint HealthCare Advisors, 9 Washington Avenue, Hamden, CT 06518
Email Address
Sign Up
We respect your privacy.
Thank you!
